A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Catalogued Reports, Reports 17727-19980 FA739G
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Towards a program in public planning and management (mimeo) (Reports 018112) (DPM 76-2), 1976 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 76-2)
  Economic development -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Politics and government -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Energy strategies for India: an assessment of new energy technologies (mimeo) (Reports 018113) (DPM 76-3), 1976 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 76-3)
  Economic development -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Technology -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Strategies for institutionalising public management education: the Indian experience (mimeo) (Reports 018114) (DPM 76-4), 1976 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 76-4)
  Public administration -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Technology -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Manual for block level planning (mimeo) (Reports 018115) (DPM 76-5), 1976 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 76-5)
  Central research cell - pilot research project in growth centres.
- Goals for urban planning with reference to programme (mimeo) (Reports 018116) (DPM 77-5), 1976 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 77-5)
  Reprinted from NAGARLOK Vol. VIII, No. 2, April-June 1976.
  Public administration -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Umemployment perspectives (mimeo) (Reports 018117) (DPM 77-9), 1977 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 77-9)
  Labor supply -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- International economic relations: research and seminar networking possibilities in Northeast and Southeast Asia (mimeo) (Reports 018118) (DPM 78-3), 1978 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 78-3)
- An experimental investigation of changes in problem-analysis ability... (mimeo) (Reports 018119) (MI 65-18), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet MI 65-18)
  India reports; Management, manpower & industry
  Industries -- India; Management -- India
- The Hindustan antibiotics, Ltd, Pimpri (mimeo), 1968 / (Reports 018120) (MI 68-5) (Box 936, Sheet MI 68-5)
- Notes on the nature of farm management (Reports 018121) (AG 59-3a), 1959 (Box 935, Sheet AG 59-3a)
  India reports; Agriculture
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Farm management -- India
- Some observations regarding associated research and evaluation of the IADP (Reports 018122) (AG 59-3b), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet AG 59-3b)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India
- Analysis and agricultural districts (Reports 018123) (AG 59-3c), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet AG 59-3c)
- Plan for an integrated information programme to assist the IADP (Reports 018124) (AG 61-3), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet AG 61-3)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- Intensive agricultural districts programme quality (certified) seed programme suggested sanction note to each state (Reports 018125) (AG 61-4), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet AG 61-4)
- Comments on 'a model plan' for a district workshop center (Reports 018126) (AG 61-5), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet AG 61-5)
- The marketing of certified hybrid maize seed in India (Reports 018127) (AG 62-1), 1962 (Box 935, Sheet AG 62-1)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Seed technology -- India
- Proposal to assist cultivators with water use and management in the intensive agricultural districts programme (Reports 018128) (AG 62-2), 1962 (Box 935, Sheet AG 62-2)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Irrigation -- India
- The why and how of soil testing (Reports 018129) (AG 62-3), 1962 (Box 935, Sheet AG 62-3)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Soil management -- India
- The efficiency of various fertilizers for paddy (Reports 018130) (AG 62-5), 1962 (Box 935, Sheet AG 62-5)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Fertilizers -- India
- Sambalpur paddy demonstration- 1962-63 (Reports 018131) (AG 63-3), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-3)
- Farm/village planning and redevelopment (Reports 018132) (AG 63-5), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-5)
  A guide to define main areas for research and action.
- Reportfrom Raplph B. Greene to H.A. Miles and Douglas Ensminger (Reports 018133) (AG 63-5a, 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-5a)
- Opportunities for advancing agricultural mechanization in India and Southeast Asia (Reports 018134) (AG 63-8), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-8)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India
- Suggestions for a modern paddy handling, storage and milling facility for Thanjavur district (Reports 018135) (AG 63-10), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-10)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Farm management -- India
- Estimated requirements for a model seed production, processing and storage unit for 100,000 acres of paddy - West Godavary District (Reports 018136) (AG 63-12), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-12)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India; Farm management -- India
- Intensive agricultural district programme - report 1961-62 (Reports 018137) (AG 63-13), 1963; Microfiche, 4 sheets. (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-13)
  Expert committee on assessment and evaluation, Ministry of Food and Agriculture (Dept of Agriculture.)
- The art of agriculture in the Thanhauur district (Reports 018138) (AG 63-13a), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-13a)
- Recommendation for establisment of a College of Agricultural Engineering at the Punjab Agricultural University, Ludhiana (Reports 018139) (AG 63-15), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-15)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India
- Some preliminary thoughts on package program information work (Reports 018140) (AG 63-16), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-16)
- Strengthening post-graduate studies in agricultural engineering at the Indian Institute of Technology, Kharagpur (Reports 018141) (AG 63-18), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-18)
- Sambalpur paddy demonstrations 1962-63 (Reports 018142) (AG 64-5), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-5)
  Agricultural innovations -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India
- Intensive agricultural district programme (Reports 018143) (AG 64-8), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-8)
  Farm management report for 1962-63 147 farms records - West Godavari District.
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India
- The intensive agricultural district program (Reports 018144) (AG 64-9), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-9)
- Composite result demonstration guide (Reports 018145) (AG64-9a), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-9a)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India
- Suggestions on revision and adoption of the first farm management extension manual in a particular country (Reports 018146) (AG 64-9b), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-9b)
- A case study of two package program villages in Aligarh District (Reports 018147) (AG 64-11), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-11)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- I.A.D.P. supply projections -fourth plan (Reports 018148) (AG 64-13), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-13)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- Farm management study - effect of tenure on use of improved production practices on paddy Tanjavur District - IADP (Reports 018149) (AG 64-17), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-17)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Agricultural education -- India
- Role of soil testing in fertiliser use (Reports 018150) (AG 64-22), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-22)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Soil management -- India; Fertilizers -- India
- The first step in advancing mechanization (Reports 018151) (AG 64-26), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-26)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India
- Soil acidity and the use of lime in India (Reports 018152) (AG 64-28), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-28)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Soil management -- India
- Using an 'information package' for intensive agriculture (Reports 018153) (AG 64-30), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-30)
- Cooperative institutions and agricultural development (Reports 018154) (AG 64-35), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-35)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- Food enough for 540 million people - India in 1970 (Reports 018155) (AG 64-36), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-36)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- Foodgrain procurement and distribution (Reports 018156) (AG 64-38), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-38)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Rice -- India; Corn -- India; Wheat -- India
- Importance of materials and other resources (Reports 018157) (AG64-40), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-40)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Agricultural engineering -- India
- Estimates of economic feasibility IADP rice mill evaluation project (Reports 018158) (AG 64-44), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-44)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural processing industries -- India
- Impressions of the Ford Foundation IADP activity in India (Reports 018159) (AG 65-7), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-7)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- The district agriculture information officer: a new key post in India's agricultural development (Reports 018160) (AG 65-8), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-8)
  Agriculture and state -- India
- A glimmer of light (Reports 018161) (AG 65-10a), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-10a)
- Justification for more power for agricultural production in India (Reports 018162) (AG 65-12), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-12)
- An improved bullock harness for increased draft potentiality (Reports 018163) (AG 65-13), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-13)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Agricultural engineering -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India
- A survey of the Indian tractor ancillary industry (Reports 018164) (AG 65-16), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-16)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India; Agricultural engineering -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India
- The distribution of chemical fertilizers in India (mimeo) (Reports 018165) (AG 65-18), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-18)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Fertilizers -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India
- Some responses of rice farmers to the package program in Tanjore District, India (Reports 018166) (AG 65-20), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-20)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Rice -- India; Agricultural laborers -- India
- Rail head godown (Reports 018167) (AG 65-22), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-22)
- Village level Godown (Reports 018168) (AG 65-23), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-23)
- Final report of my activities with IADP in India (Reports 018169) (AG 65-24b), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-24b)
- Role of long term credit in intensive agricultural development (Reports 018170) (AG 65-28), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-28)
- First annual report of progress Ford Foundation -- Ohio State University Project (Reports 018171) (AG 65-31), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-31)
- IADP fact sheet (Reports 018172) (AG 65-38a), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-38a)
- Preliminary report of programs in soil and water resoures in the College of Agricultural Engineering, Punjab Agricultural University (Reports 018173) (AG 65-40), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-40)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Soil management -- India; Irrigation -- India
- The Fertilizer Association of India (Reports 018174) (AG 65-44), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-44)
  National seminar on fertilisers soil testing.
  Agriculture and state -- India; Fertilizers -- India
- A prospective view of the intensive agricultural districts (Reports 018175) (AG 65-45), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-45)
- A Study on tenurial conditions in package districts (Reports 018176) (AG 65-46), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-46)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural credit -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- A farm to factory program for modern agricultural equipment (Reports 018177) (AG 65-47), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-47)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India
- Cereal grain production, consumption and marketing patterns (Reports 018178) (AG 65-50), 1965; Microfiche, 4 sheets. (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-50)
  Agriculture and state -- Nepal; Farm produce -- Nepal -- Marketing
- First progress report to the Ford Foundation on the Indian Institute of Technology/Kharagpur Project (Reports 018179) (AG 65-50a), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-50a)
  Financial accounting.
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Agricultural education -- India
- The cultivator's commodity marketing decisions (Reports 018180) (AG 65-63), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-63)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Farm produce -- Marketing -- India
- A challenge for the rice milling industry (Reports 018181) (AG 65-68), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-68)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Agricultural processing industries -- India
- Report of activities (Reports 018182) (AG 66-9), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-9)
  College of Agricultural Engineering Punjab Agricultural University.
- A draft fourth plan I.A.D.P. programme, Tanjavur District (Reports 018183) (AG 66-10b), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-10b)
- Package programme demonstrates techniques for speeding up application for research findings by Indian farmers (Reports 018184) (AG 66-10c), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-10c)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Farm management -- India
- Field trip summary (visit of Nepal officials to observe India's IADP program) (Reports 018185) (AG 66-13), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-13)
- Programming for future agricultural development in India (Reports 018186) (AG 66-14a), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-14a)
- Progress report - availability of production inputs IADP districts - India (Reports 018187) (AG 66-16), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-16)
- Soils, soil testing, and the efficient use of fertilizers (Reports 018188) (AG 66-17), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-17)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Soil management -- India; Fertilizers -- India; Farm management -- India
- Farm mechanization in India (Reports 018189) (AG 66-19), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-19)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India; Farm management -- India
- A rice research and graduate training centre for harvesting, handling, conditioning, processing and storage (Reports 018190) (AG 66-24), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-24)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Farm management -- India
- Some specific recommendations re: IADP districts and agricultural development (Reports 018191) (AG 66-25), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-25)
- Fourth plan expected demand and requirements (Reports 018192) (AG 66-31), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-31)
- Organization of Indian agriculture (Reports 018193) (AG 66-32), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-32)
- Fourth plan expected demand and requirements production inputs (Reports 018194) (AG 66-33), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-33)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Agricultural credit -- India; Farm management -- India
- A suggested procedure for evaluating the demonstration paddy storage and rice milling programme (Reports 018195) (AG 66-35a), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-35a)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Farm management -- India
- Paddy storage, drying and aeration (Reports 018196) (AG 66-35b), 1966 (Box 935, Sheet AG 66-35b)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Farm management -- India
- Confidential terminal report (Reports 018197) (AG 67-1), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-1)
- Recommendations for specific research and teaching programs in engineering at Punjab Agricultural University, India (Reports 018198) (AG 67-8a), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-8a)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India
- Recommendations for specific research and teaching programs in engineering at Punjab Agricultural University, India (Reports 018199) (AG 67-8b), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-8b)
- Final report to the Ford Foundation on consultancy at the Institute of Agriculture, Anand, Gujurat, India (Reports 018200) (AG 67-11), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-11)
- Comments on research - National Institute of Community Development (Reports 018201) (AG 67-19b), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-19b)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Community development -- India
- Cooperatives, credit, supplies and marketing in Ludhiana IADP District (Reports 018202) (AG 67-20), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-20)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Farm produce -- Marketing -- India; Farm management -- India
- Sambalpur district by zones (Reports 018203) (AG 67-21), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-21)
- Intensive agricultural development and aspects of Indian agriculture (Reports 018204) (AG 67-22), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-22)
- Field study in West Godavari district (Reports 018205) (AG 67-24), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-24)
  West Dodavari District IADP staff, GOI specialists, Ford Foundation IADP team, members of USAID and Andhra Pradesh Agricultural University representatives of cooperative institutions
- More rice in Thanjavur (Reports 018206) (AG 67-26a), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-26a)
  Some observations on prospects for Indian agricultural development.
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Rice -- India
- Indian extension education research unique or imitative (Reports 018207) (AG 67-27), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-27)
- The relation of intensive agriculture to increasing business (Reports 018208) (AG 67-34), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-34)
- Economists on active service (Reports 018209) (AG 67-35), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-35)
- District program development (Reports 018210) (AG 67-36), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-36)
- Experience of cultivators growing Mexican wheat in Ludhiana district (Reports 018211) (AG 67-37), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-37)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Wheat -- India; Agricultural laborers -- India
- Paddy survey in Thanjavur district (Reports 018212) (AG 67-39), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-39)
- Tanjore paddy project (Reports 018213) (AG 67-40), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-40)
- Agricultural science in India (Reports 018214) (AG 67-41), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-41)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Agricultural engineering -- India
- The challenge to rice workers in having food enough in India (Reports 018215) (AG 67-42), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-42)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural laborers -- India; Rice -- India
- Terminal report (Reports 018216) (AG 67-43), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-43)
- A successful experiment (Reports 018217) (AG 67-47), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-47)
- Ford Foundation self study of the IADP programme (Reports 018218) (AG 67-48), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-48)
- Report on the development of a College of Agricultural Engineering at Punjab Agricultural University, Ludhiana, Punjab, India from January 10 1965 to July 2, 1967 (Reports 018219) (AG 67-49), Microfiche, 6 sheets. (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-49)
- Ludhiana district - analysis of bench-mark and assessment surveys under the IADP crop-cutting schedules (Reports 018220) (AG 67-50), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-50)
- Some IADP highlights for September and October, 1967 (Reports 018221) (AG 67-51) (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-51)
- A proposed agricultural communication center at the Andhra Pradesh Agricultural University, Hyderabad, India (Reports 018222) (AG 67-53), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-53)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education; Agricultural development projects -- India; Farm management -- India
- The challenge for UPAU (Reports 018223) (AG 67-54), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-54)
- District programme development - some basic concepts (Reports 018224) (AG 67-57), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-57)
- Land and water development on the Tungabhadra project in Mysore (Reports 018225) (AG 67-59), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-59)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Farm management -- India; Irrigation -- India
- 1967 Kuruvai paddy survey in Thanjavur district (Reports 018226) (AG 67-60) (Box 935, Reel AG 67-60)
- A short note on my observations - tour programme - Ludhiana, Mandi, Tanjore, Hyderabad (Reports 018227) (AG 67-61), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-61)
- Ford IADP and its activities (Reports 018228) (AG67-63), 1967; Johnson, Sherman E. (Sherman Elbridge) (1908-1993) (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-63)
- Administrative and personnel problems (Reports 018229) (AG 67-64), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-64)
- Insuring short-term credit loans in IADP districts (Reports 018230) (AG 67-65), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-35)
- Intensive agricultural programs (Reports 018231) (AG 67-68), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-68)
- Paddy production training programme (Reports 018232) (AG 67-69), 1967 (Box 935, Sheet AG 67-69)
- Working together for a more effective overall IADP (Reports 018233) (AG 68-1f), 1968 (Box 935, Sheet AG 68-1f)
  Sent to all IADP Ford Foundation consultants and GOI specialists.
- State level seminar on intensive agricultural district programme (Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh) (Reports 018234) (AG 68-16), 1968 (Box 935, Sheet AG 68-16)
- Terminal report (Reports 018235) (AG 68-17), 1968 (Box 935, Sheet AG 68-17)
- Extension work in farm mechanization for Afpro Project Holders (Reports 018236) (AG 68-18), 1968 (Box 935, Sheet AG 68-18)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India
- A brief report on the All India Coordinated Wheat Scheme - the 1968 harvest (Reports 018237) (AG 68-21a) (Box 935, Sheet AG 68-21a)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Wheat -- India; Farm produce -- India
- Benchmark report - rice mill program (Reports 018238) (AG 68-26), 1968 (Box 935, Sheet AG 68-26)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Rice -- India; Farm produce -- India
- Some thoughts regarding our priorities (Reports 018239) (AG 68-27), 1968 (Box 935, Sheet AG 68-27)
- Terminal report (Reports 018240) (AG 68-28a), 1968 (Box 935, Sheet AG 68-28a)